homebargains.co.uk 2017-05-08

# Home Bargains. Privacy Policy

**Home Bargains Privacy Policy**

Home Bargains is committed to protecting your privacy. The following Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. You should read this privacy policy carefully. By accessing and continuing to use the Home Bargains Website you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to the terms of this privacy policy. 

**  Business Information **

** ** Home Bargains is the store/brand name of TJ Morris Ltd. TJ Morris Ltd is registered in England and Wales (company registration number 01505036)  at Axis Business Park, East Lancashire Road, Gillmoss, Liverpool, L11 0JA. Its registered VAT number is 320093700. 

**  Information Collected **

** ** We collect information provided by you when you use our Website, including, and without limitation: 

·          Information at the time of registering and setting up your account, subscribing to our newsletter, making a complaint or reporting a problem with the website and any other services that we may offer from time to time. 

·          Information provided if you contact us in writing or over the phone, we may keep a record of all communications. 

·          Details of your transactions on the Home Bargains Website and of the fulfilment of your orders. 

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by Home Bargains. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site in order to improve the service we provide to our customers. 

You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. 

**Disclosures of Your Information**

Home Bargains will not pass your personal information to anyone else, except: 

·          Where we are required or permitted to do so by law. 

·          To a member of our group of companies. 

·          To a third party suppliers who assist us in performing our services to you such as our delivery companies and card processing partners. 

**Use of Your Information** ****

The information Home Bargains collects will be used to process your orders and to help us ensure that all customers are genuine, including: 

·          To fulfil our obligations arising from any transactions you place with us. 

·          To notify you about changes to our services. 

·          To maintain and administer any registered account that you hold with us. 

·          To send offers and news about Home Bargains products. 

**Security and Storage of Information**

We will keep your information secure by taking appropriate technical and organisational measures against its unauthorised or unlawful processing and against its accidental loss, destruction or damage.

We will store your information at least for the duration of any relationship we have with you, or as otherwise required by law (normally up to a maximum of 7 years for legal and tax reasons). 

**Cookies**

We use a feature of your internet browser called a ‘cookie’ on this website.  A ‘cookie’ is a very small text file that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive which allows us to help you get the best out of your visit to the website. Home Bargains uses cookies for a number of purposes, for instance: 

·          To enable us to simplify the logging on process for registered users. 

·          To help ensure the security and authenticity of registered users 

·          To provide the mechanisms for online shopping and to enable traffic monitoring. 

·          Our cookies will never store passwords or credit card information. 

For further information about cookies please visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

** ** **Other Web Sites**

The Home Bargains Web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. The operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. Home Bargains will not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page and, will take effect immediately. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. ****

**Access Rights**

If you would like to obtain a copy of the information we have about you please contact customer services and make an access request. All access requests will be subject to an administration fee of £10 to provide you with details of the information we hold about you. 

You also have a right to be removed from any mailing list we hold at any time. To do this please edit your profile in the “My Account” section or use the _unsubscribe_ link on the email mailing.
